linksystems-uk.com 2014-07-12

# Privacy Policy

LCS Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy

At Link Communications Systems Ltd. ("LCS," "we," "us," or "our"), we respect the privacy of your information, and have provided this explanation about our online information practices to show our commitment to protecting your privacy. By using this website (the "Website") or the services provided through this Website or otherwise provided by LCS (the "Services"), we may collect information about you, and use and disclose such information, as described in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). This Privacy Policy describes LCS’s use of Personal Information and Anonymous Information (each as defined below) that we collect when you (whether you are an individual or a company) use the Website or Services, as well as information we may use to update the information you provide to us through other means. "Personal Information" means your contact information (i.e., your name, address, email address, or telephone number) and any other non-public information that is associated with your contact information. "Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information.

BY USING THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES ARE HOSTED IN THE UNITED STATES AND ARE INTENDED FOR AND DIRECTED TO USERS IN THE UNITED STATES. IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE, THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, WHICH IS GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND OUR SERVICES AGREEMENT, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER.

Children Under 18

The Website is not directed to children and children are not eligible to use our Services. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. We do not collect or maintain Personal Information from people we actually know are under 18 years old, and no part of the Website or Services is designed to attract people under 18 years old. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 18 years old, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our databases.

The Information We Collect

The Personal Information we gather from you helps us learn more about, and provide you with, the use of the Website or Services. We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily in the course of correspondence, registration and as otherwise identified below. In addition, we collect certain Anonymous Information which cannot be used to personally identify any user, such as aggregate or statistical data.

In order to use some Services, you may be required to complete the applicable registration form accessible on the Website. When you register with us, we collect and maintain a record of all data and Personal Information provided, such as your name, email address, phone number, and in some cases credit card or other payment information when you order Services online.

For some Services, a registered user may be provided a unique username and password that enables access to the Services. We may track the use of those usernames and passwords in order to collect and maintain records of individual transactions conducted through the Services.

When you send us a communication, or fill out a request form such as a survey or contact request, we will collect all information contained therein. We collect and store Personal Information you may provide when applying for a position with LCS, which (depending on the circumstances), can include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, desired salary, education level, professional experience and other Personal Information. We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone, fax or email, from third-parties that provide services for us in connection with the Website or Services, as well as from third parties to whom you have voluntarily provided information. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via the Website or Services. This Privacy Policy does not restrict our use of that additional information. By providing the above information voluntarily, you give us permission to use such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Anonymous Information Collected Via Technology

As you use the Website or Services, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our or our service providers’ server logs, such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, etc. We may also use Cookies (as defined below) and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed. This type of information is collected to make the Website or Services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the experience with the Website or Services to meet your special interests and needs.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We, or our service providers, may track your IP Address when you access the Website or Services. For example, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our Website and to enhance our Website based on the usage pattern data we receive.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience with the Website or Services. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website or Services may not work properly.

The Ways We Use Information

In general, we use Personal Information that you submit to us either to administer your account, carry out our obligations arising from any agreement you may have with us, act on and improve our outreach and educational efforts, to statistically analyze Website usage, to improve our content, features and performance, to customize our Website’s content and layout, and to provide you with support and access to our Website and Services. We may use your Personal Information to respond to your requests or deliver information that you opt-in to receive from us or our partners. In some cases, this information is targeted to your interests, such as e-mail alerts and news updates. We will not send you promotions or announcements unless you ask or give us permission to do so. You can opt out of receiving promotional information by so indicating in your registration/preferences file, or by following the opt-out procedures contained within the e-mails and news updates that we provide to you. If you voluntarily provide us with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, we may use this information to customize and otherwise provide our Services to you. Additionally, we use your e-mail address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to your use of the Website and Services. During the term of our agreement with you, we retain the right to send you service-related communications.

The Ways We Disclose Information

It is our general policy to restrict who can access Personal Information. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share the Personal Information that we collect with third-parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

We may provide your Personal Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of the Website or Services and to help us communicate with you. Examples of such services include hosting our Website, sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. These third-parties are required not to disclose your Personal Information and not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the relevant services to us.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name or email address) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may use Anonymous Information to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance the Website or Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third-parties in our discretion.

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may share some or all of your Personal information with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates"), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event LCS goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of LCS or its assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may share some or all of your Anonymous Information or Personal Information with our third-party partners, other third-parties to whom you ask us to send your information, or about whom you are otherwise notified and do not request to opt out of such sharing. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of your personally identifiable information by such third-parties. LCS does not maintain responsibility for the manner in which third-parties use or further disclose your personally identifiable information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy, after we have disclosed such information to those third-parties. If you do not want LCS to use or disclose Personal Information collected about you in the manners identified in this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website or Services.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Use; (b) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (c) protect and defend the rights or property of LCS, you, or third-parties. You hereby consent to LCS sharing your Personal Information under the circumstances described herein.

Security

We employ reasonable physical, electronic and managerial security methods to help protect against unauthorized access to Personal Information, and maintain data accuracy. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of information about you at any time, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal data or non-personal data arising in connection with the theft thereof.

How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information

Registered users may update Personal Information submitted previously by contacting us. Subsequent uses or disclosures of information by us will reflect those changes, but we have no ability to update any information previously disclosed to any third-party. Certain information is necessary in order for us to provide the Website or Services; therefore, if you delete such necessary information you may not be able to use the Website or Services.

If you wish to have your Personal Information removed from our databases, you may contact us at [info@linksystems-uk.com](mailto:info@linksystems-uk.com) and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, telephone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Within a reasonable time after we receive your request, we will remove the Personal Information. Please note that even though you may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, we may be required (by law or otherwise, such as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, or troubleshoot problems) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time) in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

Third Party Practices

The Site or Services may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. The privacy policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our Site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policy for each third-party website you visit before responding to any offers. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site or Services and does not apply to these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third-parties from the Site or Services, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their services, other websites, locations or their content.

Changes to Our Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted to our Website at least fifteen (15) days in advance of their effective date. Personal Information collected before changes are made will be processed according to the previous Privacy Policy that it was collected under. By using our Website or Services, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.

Contact Us.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at [info@linksystems-uk.com](mailto:info@linksystems-uk.com).
